Okay, so we now have a page that works.
We can click, we can remove cards, but I
want to show you a weakness of this
page. So, let's create phto and we'll
say super high energy. And then we'll
upload a profile picture for him
and we'll do dog picture two and we'll
add the dog. Okay, now we've got our dog
with super high energy. I can click this
dog and get rid of it. I can click this
dog and get rid of it. But when I click
this one, I can't get rid of it. Why?
Because it doesn't have an event
handler. So if I inspect this code, it's
got a div class card. But here where it
would have an on click, it's not there.
Um, and if you look at the other ones
that we created, we added an on click
with the remove me function called. So,
if we want to do that, we can do that
the same way we did all of the other
things where we set the value, we set
the text context. Um, we can access the
new element that we're creating, which
we've called new card,
and then we need to query selector it.
Um, the thing we're looking for is a div
with an ID with a class of card cuz
that's where we want to put the event
handler. And then we want to say add
event listener.
This takes in um can take in a couple of
things, but the first one it takes in is
what type of event are we handling. In
this case, we're going to handle the
click. So, anywhere that you had on um
up above where you said like on click on
mouse down, you'll just type it without
the on down here. So, I say when you
click it and then you put a comma and it
says what function do you want me to
call? And the function we want to call
is remove me. Now, when they click it,
it will call the remove me function and
it will remove the item. So, if we save
this and we come back over, we can add
our dog.
Super happy dog. And we can choose a
profile picture
and we'll
add our dog. Now, we can also remove the
dog. And the way that worked is because
we attached an event listener. Um, we
said when this event happens, call this
function, pass in the event, and then
you can use whatever is part of that
event to figure out which element to F.